You said it was a mistake, the numbers were okay,
and the guidance wasn't anything special.
They've lowered their margin guidance a bit,
and all the IT companies have done the same,
but their morning guidance is
at the low end of expectations.
What's the situation with the brokerage? From a large perspective, there's a
lot of comfort, so there's
no rating change here. The target for the currency is
1370. They believe that the product business is the
driver. If we look at the results, consider the
mix and margin. If you
look at this product-platform
business, you have a lot of margin growth, which is
why you've earned the printed margin,
and the division is a little weak. But going forward, you'll have to keep an
eye on service, which could be a
driver. The target for the company has been raised to
1360 rupees. They believe
that the growth of 12 to 14 percent is
good, but the margin
guidance is weak, and that's why
they've cut their target estimates by 6 to 7 percent.
Let's talk with
Morgan Stanley. Yes, Android
is the target.  rs.900 Amargarh Shaili, however,
believes that the execution
of the company for the quarter is good, there is no
positive surprise anywhere, but if we
talk about the group now, it is mixed because
select verticals are doing well,
only the children and the tortoises are weakening, so
you do not see this every day
and going forward, you may see supply side
changes dominating the company,
in this situation and the guidance can be given,
but if we see, Bakri has
not made any major change in its rating target here,
so from such a point, the bike of Param Organ Celebration has
another target of ₹17,100, however,
if we see, they have missed by about nine to ten
seconds, Cancer Mughal soldiers have been
intimated, although the management and guide
are good, now the management feels that
their market share can improve from here
and from topline growth they have given
guidance for 523, now somewhere
if the results are there, you may like them
because of underwriting and investment games  It may appear that
a mixed
bike group remained in Cuttack,
although the guidance may be
professional, your enemy got
artists
Jhal